Guide to the Pierce County Central Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Pierce County Central Labor Council records, 1942-1989; 1947-1986; 2882-004; 15 cubic feet (15 boxes)
  - Series II: Correspondence, 1947-1989 (Box-folder 3/1-3/39; 4/1-4/34; 6/9-6/30; 7/1-7/18; 7/20-7/23; 8/1-8/21; 9/1; 10/13-10/23; 11/1-11/11; 12/1-12/7; 13/12; 13/14-13/16; 13/18-13/28; 14/1-14/4)
    - Subseries A: Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1974 (Box-folder 3/1-3/7; 4/1-4/3)
      - Outgoing Correspondence (6 of 7), 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Outgoing Correspondence (7 of 7), 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Outgoing Correspondence (1 of 3), 1947-1974 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Outgoing Correspondence (2 of 3), 1947-1974 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Outgoing Correspondence (3 of 3), 1947-1974 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Subseries B: Incoming Correspondence, 1968-1984 (Box-folder 4/7-4/34; 7/9)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "A", 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "B", 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "C" (1 of 3), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "C" (2 of 3), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "C" (3 of 3), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "D", 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "E", 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "F", 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "G", 1969 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "H", 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "I", 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "J", 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "K", 1970-1972 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "L", 1969-1984 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "M", 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "N", 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "O", 1968-1974 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "P" (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "P" (2 of 2), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "R", 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4/26)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "S", 1970-1973 (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "T" (1 of 2), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/28)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "T" (2 of 2), 1971-1973 (Box-folder 4/29)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "U", 1968-1973 (Box-folder 4/30)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "V", 1969-1974 (Box-folder 4/31)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "W" (1 of 2), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "W" (2 of 2), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Incoming Correspondence A-Z; "X-Y-Z", 1972-1974 (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Incoming Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Subseries C: Correspondence A-Z, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 6/9-6/16; 6/18-6/28)
      - Correspondence F, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Correspondence G, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Correspondence H, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Correspondence I, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Correspondence J, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Correspondence K, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Correspondence L, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Correspondence M, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - Correspondence S, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/18)
      - Correspondence T, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Correspondence Tacoma Public Schools, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Correspondence U, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Correspondence United Way (1 of 3), 1978-1983 (Box-folder 6/22)
      - Correspondence United Way (2 of 3), 1978-1983 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Correspondence United Way (3 of 3), 1978-1983 (Box-folder 6/24)
      - United Way Campaign 1982 (Box-folder 6/25)
      - Correspondence W (1 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/26)
      - Correspondence W (2 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/27)
      - Correspondence X-Y-Z, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - Subseries D: Correspondence with the Washington State Labor Council, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 7/1-7/8; 7/16-7/18; 7/20-7/23)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council (1 of 6), 1989 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council (2 of 6), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council (3 of 6), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council (4 of 6), 1988 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council (5 of 6), 1988 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council (6 of 6), 1988 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council, 1984 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Correspondence Washington State Labor Council, 1983 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, Washington State Labor Council, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, Washington State Labor Council and Washington Federation of Teachers, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, Washington State Labor Council, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, Washington State Labor Council, 1982 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, Washington State Labor Council, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, Washington State Labor Council and Associated Committees, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, Washington State Labor Council and Associated Committees, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Subseries E: Correspondence with the American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1947-1987 (Box-folder 3/11-3/13; 4/5-4/6; 8/1-8/21; 9/1; 10/13-10/23; 12/1-12/7; 13/19-13/21; 13/23; 13/27)
      - Incoming Correspondence American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Incoming/Outgoing Correspondence AFL-CIO (1 of 2), 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Incoming/Outgoing Correspondence AFL-CIO (2 of 2), 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Incoming Correspondence American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Incoming Correspondence American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (1 of 2), 1972 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1980 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1978 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO: Union Label & Service Trades Department: Boycotts, Purchasing Union-Made Goods, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 10/20)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO: Union Label & Service Trades Department: Boycotts, Purchasing Union-Made Goods, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO: Union Label & Service Trades Department: Boycotts, Purchasing Union-Made Goods, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO: Solidarity Day in Washington, DC, 1981 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - Incoming Correspondence, AFL-CIO: Boycotts, including asparagus boycott in Washington state, 1986 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO: Boycotts, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO; Clippings and notes from AFL-CIO President Lane Kirkland's visit to Portland/Tacoma, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence, AFL-CIO, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Correspondence-AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Correspondence-AFL-CIO, 1974 (Box-folder 13/20)
      - Correspondence-AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Correspondence-Pierce County Labor Council & AFL-CIO, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 13/23)
      - CorrespondencePierce County Central Labor Council & AFL-CIO, 1977-1977 (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Subseries F: General Correspondence, 1947-1987 (Box-folder 3/8-3/10; 3/14-3/39; 4/4; 6/17; 6/29-6/30; 7/10-7/15; 11/1-11/11; 13/12; 13/14-13/16; 13/18; 13/22; 13/24-13/26; 13/28; 14/1-14/4)
      - Incoming/Outgoing Correspondence, 1949-1973 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Endorsements and Representation Authorizations, 1947-1972 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Pierce County Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO Vets Manpower Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Incoming/Outgoing Correspondence Building Trade Council "We Don't Patronize", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "A", 1948-1973 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "B", 1948-1973 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "C", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "D", 1947-1971 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "E", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "F", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "G", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "H", 1948-1973 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "I", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "J", 1950-1973 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "K", 1949-1973 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "L", 1948-1973 (Box-folder 3/26)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "M", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "Mc", 1951-1973 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "N", 1947-1969 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "O", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/30)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "P", 1948-1973 (Box-folder 3/31)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "R", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/32)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "S", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/33)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "T", 1947-1973 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "U", 1947-1972 (Box-folder 3/35)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "V", 1948-1970 (Box-folder 3/36)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "W", 1948-1973 (Box-folder 3/37)
      - Correspondence Regarding "We Don't Patronize" Companies Beginning with "X-Y-Z", 1950-1967 (Box-folder 3/38)
      - Labor Day Addresses, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 3/39)
      - Tacoma Federation of Teachers # 461 Paraprofessionals Correspondence and Draft Agreements, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Correspondence Reports and Correspondence on Committee for Gifted Education, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - Correspondence City Of Tacoma ( Part I), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/29)
      - Correspondence City Of Tacoma (Part II), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/30)
      - Correspondence: Pierce County Government, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Correspondence: Pierce County Government, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Correspondence: Secretary-Treasurer Clyde Hupp, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Correspondence: Political Action, Retiree Organizing, and Executive Board, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Correspondence: Other Labor Organizations and Programs, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Correspondence: Other Labor Organizations and Programs, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Coalition of Labor Union Women, Consumer Alliance for Insurance Reform, Pierce County Central Labor Council], 1982-1986 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Pierce County Central Labor Council, Boeing Commercial Airplane Company, American Red Cross], 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Environmental Protection Agency, American Federation of Government Employees, Pierce County Central Labor Council], 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Job Service Employers Committee, King County Labor Council, Department of Labor and Industry], 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Department and Labor Industries, Board of Industrial Insurance Appeals], 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Northwest Power Planning Council, Pierce County Central Labor Council, Puget Sound Air Pllution Control Agency, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Puget Sound Air Pollution Control Agency, Pierce County Central Labor Council, American Red Cross, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Pierce County Central Labor Council, Snohomish County Labor Council, Superintendent of Public Instruction, Tacoma News Tribune, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Washington Federation of Teachers, Department of City Clerk/General Services, Tacoma Public Schools, Unemployment Law Project], 1982-1987 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Unemployment Law Project, Washington State University, 1984 Pacific Northwest World Trade Expo], 1983-1987 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence [Washington Council on International Trade, Pierce County: Our Stake in International Trade, Washington State Labor Council, YWCA], 1983-1984 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - CorrespondenceSwedberg Suit, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Correspondence & NoticesLegislation, 1977 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Promotional MaterialsLabor Studies, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - CorrespondenceL.H. Pedersen, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Correspondence-Organizations Beginning with A, L.H. Pedersen: Correspondence with Affiliated Unions and Other Labor Organizations, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Correspondence-Pierce County Central Labor Council, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Correspondence-Pierce County Central Labor Council, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Correspondence-Pierce County Central Labor Council: Aberdeen Education Association and Local 313 Strikes, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 13/25)
      - Correspondence-Pierce County Central Labor Council: Tacoma Public Schools, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 13/26)
      - CorrespondencePierce County Central Labor Council, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - CorrespondencePierce County Central Labor Council, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - CorrespondencePierce County Central Labor Council, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Correspondence, Posters, and PamphletsPierce County Central Labor Council & Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1973-1977 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - CorrespondencePierce County Central Labor Council, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Series III: Financial Records, 1937-1982 (Box-folder 3/40-3/41; 6/1-6/8; 14/5)
    - Profit & Loss Statements, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 3/40)
    - Card and Label Council of Tacoma Financial Statements, 1951-1973 (Box-folder 3/41)
    - Monthly Expense Voucher, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Bills Central Labor Council, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Invoices (1 of 2) (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Invoices (2 of 2), 1979-1983 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - The Stationers Inc Invoices, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Copy Machine Reports, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Central Labor Council Bank Reconciliation Documents, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Central Labor Council Financial Statements, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Pierce County Central Labor Council Closed Bank Books, 1937-1977 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Series IV: Related Corporate Bodies, Committees, and Projects, 1942-1986 (Box-folder 5/1-5/34; 7/19; 9/2-9/21; 10/1-10/11; 12/8-12/28; 13/1-13/11; 13/17; 14/6-14/23; 15/1-15/21)
    - Subseries A: Union Label Council, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 5/26-5/34)
      - Union Label & Service Trade Correspondence, News Release & Brochures (1 of 2), 1979-1983 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - Union Label & Service Trade Correspondence, News Release & Brochures (2 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 5/27)
      - Minutes Union Label & Service Trade Council, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 5/28)
      - Labor Letter Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 5/29)
      - Documents Referred to Trustees, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 5/30)
      - Union Label Catalog, 1980 (Box-folder 5/31)
      - Iowa Beef Processors Strike, 1982 (Box-folder 5/32)
      - "Us Trade Policies: Labor's Position" & Union Label fliers, circa 1979 (Box-folder 5/33)
      - Union Label & Service Trade Correspondence, News Release & Brochures, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - Subseries B: Labor Advocate Publishing, 1942-1983 (Box-folder 5/1-5/25; 13/17)
      - Labor Advocate By Laws, Voting Trust Agreement, and Shareholder Minutes (1 of 2), 1942-1971 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Labor Advocate By Laws, Voting Trust Agreement, and Shareholder Minutes (2 of 2), 1942-1971 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Northwest Administrators Transfer Account Employees Dental Trust, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - CTM Electrical Contractors Statements International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Benefit Fund Clyde Hupp, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Financial Reports, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Western States Office of Professional Employee's Pension Fund, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Payroll Book, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Incoming Correspondence A, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Incoming Correspondence Apprenticeship & Training Council (1 of 2), 1980-1982 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Incoming Correspondence Apprenticeship & Training Council (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Incoming Correspondence Auto Trade Strike, 1978 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Incoming Correspondence B, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Incoming Correspondence C, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Incoming correspondence Channel 13 Sale, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Incoming Correspondence Coors Boycott, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Incoming Correspondence D, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Incoming Correspondence E, 1977 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Incoming Correspondence F, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Union Card and Label Council Correspondence and Financial Statements, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Committee on Political Education C4's, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Central Labor Council Financial Statements Balance Sheets, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Roll Call of Officers, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Payroll Book, 1977 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Labor Advocate Dissolution and Financial Statements, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Labor Advocate Financial Statements, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Tacoma Labor Advocate & Labor Advocate Publishing Company: Ledgers, Correspondence, Donation Records, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Subseries C: Building Project: New Labor Center, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 12/13-12/28; 13/1-13/11)
      - Project Specifications: Electrical Set (E-1) & Mechanical Set (M-1), for new Labor Center/Temple, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - General Construction Project Specifications (GC-2), for new Labor Center/Temple, 1970 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - General Construction Project Specifications (GC-1), for new Labor Center/Temple, 1970 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Air Conditioning Contract Bid, for new Labor Center/Temple, 1973 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Correspondence, Invoices, Plans: Labor Center, Room 211, 1972 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - New Rent Charges & Square Footage, for new Labor Center/Temple, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Correspondence, Labor Center Construction, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Urban Renewal: Relocation Instructions, Inventories, Income Statements, Property Appraisals, Leases, and the Urban Renewal Plan, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Records of Payment & Change Orders, Strom Construction, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 12/21)
      - Records of Payment & Agreements, Architects Johnson, Austin, Berg, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Legal Documents & Correspondence, Attorneys-at-Law Paul Sinnit & Carl Teitge (1 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Legal Documents & Correspondence, Attorneys-at-Law Paul Sinnit & Carl Teitge (2 of 2), 1970-1974 (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Parking Strip, 1972 (Box-folder 12/25)
      - Lights and Windows, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 12/26)
      - Testing Lab, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 12/27)
      - Sound Elevator Company, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 12/28)
      - Audited Financial Statements-Labor Temple Corporation & Pierce County Central Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 13/1)